cherrycredits.com 2016-12-05

# Cherry Credits

At Cherry Credits, we value the importance of your privacy. Our Privacy Policy covers the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be received or collected when registering with Cherry Credits or using any of our services and also some of the measures we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.

By accessing our websites and / or using the materials, facilities and / or services offered through our websites, you agree that, Singapore law (including without Limitation, the provisions of the Evidence Act (Cap. 97), the Electronic Transactions Act (Cap. 88) and the Personal Data Protection Act (PDPA) shall govern such access and the provision of such materials, facilities and/or services and you agree to submit to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the Singapore courts.

Upon submission of your personal identifiable information on or through this website, you are giving us your consent to collect, use and disclose your personal identifiable information in the manner as set forth in our Privacy Policy.

### Why we collect personal information?

Your personal information are collected when you register a Cherry account with us. Some of these information are essential for us to verify your identity should there be a need for any form of identity verification. Your personal information also enables us to provide you convenient access to our products and services and focus on categories which may be of interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us to keep you informed on our latest announcements, updates, and events. If you do not want us to keep you up-to-date with our latest news and services, you may edit your preferences in your Cherry account.

### What information we collect and how we may use it?

  * We will request for your personal information when you register with us. To safeguard your account, certain essential information is collected to allow us to verify that you are the genuine owner of a specific Cherry account.
  * We may at times, need to share your information in order to provide the product or service you have requested.
  * We may at times, need to send your information to companies who work on behalf of Cherry Credits to provide a product or service to you. (Unless explicitly specified, these companies DO NOT have any rights to use any information we provide to them beyond what is necessary)
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process.
  * We find that your actions violate the use of our products and services.
  * We may use such information during our auditing, research, and analysis process to improve our products and services.

### Your Cherry account and related information

Cherry Credits allows you to create a Cherry account using on your personal information. This registration allows you to access our products and services. Should you need to make a purchase transaction, all you need is to login into your Cherry account.

### How we protect your personal information

We take great precautions to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

We uses Transport Layer Security (TLS) 1.2 encryption on all web pages where personal information is required. In order to make any purchase, you must use an TLS-enabled browser such as Microsoft Edge, Firefox or Chrome etc. Doing so protects the confidentiality of your personal and payment information while it's transmitted over the Internet.

You can also help us by taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords regularly and make sure you use a secure web browser. In addition, never reveal to any one your 6-digit security PIN and secret question / answer.

### Integrity of your personal information

It is very important to ensure that all submitted personal information during registration is accurate, complete, and up to date for the purposes for which it is used. Please note that while you have the right to access, correct and update personal information, certain information are non-changeable upon submission for security reasons. Do ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate by updating your Cherry account when necessary.

Your email address provided may be used to inform you of our latest news and announcements. You may opt out of this by unchecking the newsletter box during registration or choosing to unsubscribe from our mailing list.

### Links to Third Party Sites

Our website may contain links to or references to other websites that may be accessed or which may originate outside the boundaries of our websites and which information we will have no control. Cherry Credits shall have no obligation or responsibility regarding any content derived, obtained, accessed within through or outside of our websites. Any inclusion of links to such external website does not imply any endorsement or verification of the material on such website or any association with their operators, and such website shall be accessed at your own risk.

### Privacy questions

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or your personal data, please contact us via Cherry Messenger. Alternatively, you may email us at [dpo@cherrycredits.com](mailto:dpo@cherrycredits.com). 

3 Fusionopolis Way Symbiosis #11-05   
Singapore 138633   
Office Contact: 6747 6676   
Customer Service Contact: [gardener at cherrycredits dot com](mailto:gardener@cherrycredits.com)

### Revisions to the Privacy Policy

We may change or update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Please review the latest version of our Privacy Policy posted on this webpage. The changes that are posted shall take effect immediately. Please contact us at [dpo@cherrycredits.com](mailto:dpo@cherrycredits.com) if you no longer wish for us to collect, use or disclose your personal identifiable information
